kidzui.com 2014-11-02

# KidZui Privacy Policy

Effective July 1, 2013

Welcome to www.kidzui.com (“we,” “our” or “us”). This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) is provided to help ensure a rewarding online experience for all visitors to our website (the “Website”).

At www.kidzui.com, we take the privacy of every child seriously. We treat your information with care and are committed to providing a fun, safe and secure Website for visitors (hereafter "you", "visitors" or "users") to the Website. This Policy describes our online information practices, including the type of information collected on the Website, how such information is used and stored and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. By using this Website, you and, if applicable, your parent or legal guardian, agree to be bound by this Policy.

We reserve the right to change our Policy, and if we do, we will post the changes here. If we make any material changes to our Policy (for example, we significantly change the way we handle information previously collected, if any, or we change the type of information we collect), we will notify you and if necessary obtain permission of your parent or guardian.

This Policy applies only to the Website and does not apply to any other website operated by us or any affiliated company.

The Website enables users who register (as described more fully below) to download the Kidzui browser which has been designed to provide kids with a safe and secure Internet browsing experience. The vast majority of users downloading the Kidzui browser are parents seeking a safe way for their children to explore the Internet. The Kidzui browser responds to this need by permitting users to access only pre-screened websites with child appropriate content.

## I. THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

There are three general categories of information collected from Website visitors:

(a) user information requested by the Website ("User Information"),

(b) information collected by the Website from the electronic device (e.g., computer, laptop, tablet, smart phone) and Internet browser which the visitor is using to access the Website ("Computer Information"), and

(c) information collected by third-party advertisers, website analytics providers and other partners ("Third-Party Information") to whom we have granted access to the Website.

(a) User Information

1\. Do we collect information from you to use or register on our site?

Registration for kidzui.com is not required. Kids can use and enjoy the site anonymously without registration. However, in order to download and use the KidZui browser, the user must register and provide the following information: a screen name, gender, date of birth and first name as well as the email address of a parent or guardian.

We do not collect or store any Personal Information (1) about visitors to our Website until we receive consent from the parent or guardian. At the time a child 12 or under registers with KidZui.com and downloads the KidZui browser, we send an email to the child’s parent or guardian. We require that such parent or guardian give express permission in writing before we will permit the child to use any feature on KidZui.com, including the KidZui browser. If KidZui does not receive written permission from the parent or guardian of the child 12 or under, we will assume that the parent or guardian has not consented to the child being registered with the Website. We will then delete all information we have received from the child. Once the parent or guardian consents in writing to the child's registration, the child will be permitted to use any registration-based features on the Website..

2\. What types of community or social features do we offer you on our site and how do we keep these areas safe?

The Website does not allow for open messaging between its users, nor does it allow for the use of third party social networks. While the Website does allow its users to “rate” content, we do not currently provide users the ability to upload user- generated content to the site.

3\. Do we offer other features on our site that ask you to provide information?

On occasion, we may run contests or polls created by us or by third-party partners and/or advertisers. If we conduct a contest or sweepstakes on our Website, we will collect email addresses from entrants so that we may contact the winners of the contest or sweepstakes. Any email addresses collected from entrants to a contest or sweepstakes will be used on a one-time basis. After the contest or sweepstakes prizing has been awarded, we will remove the email addresses collected with respect to the contest or sweepstakes from the applicable Website database. If we collect and store any other Personal Information in addition to the user's contact information as part of these activities, we will first ask for parental permission.

(b) Computer Information.

4\. Do we collect information from you using cookies or other web technologies?

The Website uses technologies, including cookies, to help make the site faster and easier for kids to use. For example, we may use cookies to “cache” (i.e., remember) content for users and store user preferences such as passwords thereby eliminating the need to constantly re-enter data. "Cookies" may also assist us in saving your online game settings and your media player settings for facilitating future viewing of streaming content. Section II below on "Cookies and Web Beacons" will provide further information on how Computer Information may be collected from your electronic device and Internet browser and how you can use your browser settings to limit the effectiveness of Website cookies.

We also use cookies to track the activity of our users of the Website. The information regarding the activities of users on our Website is collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis and does not personally identify users, by itself or in combination with other information. Such non-personally identifiable information assists us in the internal operation of our Website and helps us improve the design and content of our Website to provide visitors with a better experience.

The Website uses third-party analytics software to provide us with information regarding the usage of the Website. The information we receive from such third-party analytic software is not Personal Information attributable to any user but rather information that is aggregated by the software so that we can track such things as how many users we have of the Website on a daily, weekly or monthly basis, what Website content or features our users are frequenting and the general geographic locations of our users.

We also gather usage data regarding your child’s Internet activity via the KidZui browser, including what web pages they visit or share, what pictures and videos they view or share, searches (and results of such searches), content they rate, tag and select as their favorites, as well as time spent online. We make this information available to parents so that parents can monitor the Internet activity of their child.

The Website does not use cookies or other technologies to track user activity for behavioral advertising (2) purposes.

(c) Third-Party Information.

5\. Do we have advertisements or e-commerce on our site?

Our Website contains advertisements which we review to make certain that such advertisements are appropriate for our audience. We explicitly label all advertising on the Website so that it will be clear to Website visitors that they are viewing advertisements. We do not permit behavioral advertising on the Website. We do not currently offer e-commerce on the Website.

Third-party advertising networks and business partners may also place advertisements on the Website and may track the responses to these advertisements. These third- parties may view, edit or place cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to help present advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. We do not permit any third party advertisers to collect Personal Information from our site. We do, however, permit third-party advertisers to track the source of users who click on the third party advertisements and go to the advertiser 's site.

6\. How does the Kidzui browser work?

The Kidzui browser enables children to navigate the Internet using a search engine that is specially adapted to only permit the child to visit carefully pre–screened websites ("third-party websites") containing child appropriate content. Please understand that our Policy does not apply to those third party websites accessed by means of the Kidzui browser. The third-party websites reached using the Kidzui browser may follow different practices and procedures with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information from those persons visiting their websites. The Kidzui browser does not pre-screen third-party websites for compliance with COPPA. We, therefore, encourage you to review the privacy policies of such third-party websites.

We also provide access to our Website to third party analytics providers. These third parties assist us in measuring, analyzing and improving the internal operations of the Website. These third parties gather information in the aggregate with respect to visitors to the Website, the pages of the Website and advertisements which are viewed by the visitors, and other information with respect to the Internet activities of visitors. These analytics providers do not collect Personal Information.

## II. COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS

To enhance your online experience, our Website uses a software technology called "cookies" which are small text files placed in visitors' computer browsers to store their preferences. As noted earlier, we use cookies to improve the user's experience on our Website and to assist us in the internal operations of our Website. Our third party service providers and/or our partners also may use cookies to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through the Website. The cookies used on our Website do not contain or collect any Personal Information.

We and our third party service providers and/or partners may also use other tracking technologies such as "Web beacons" or clear .gifs. These are small pieces of computer code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver cookies to the browsers of visitors viewing that page. We, our third party service providers and/or our partners may use web beacons on our Website from time to time to help present advertisements and measure their effectiveness.

By visiting our Website, you acknowledge, and agree that you are giving us your consent to track your activities using cookies, web beacons and related technologies. We do not, however, use tracking technologies to collect Personal Information from visitors to our Website.

You can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar tracking technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies will affect your online experience and may prevent you from enjoying the full features offered at our Website and other websites. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information on how to change the settings of your browser to limit or block the use of cookies and other tracking technology by our Website or other websites.

## III. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

7\. With whom do we share your information?

We do not share or sell any Personal Information on specific users with independent third parties, including advertisers. We use the information collected only to permit children to use the functions of KidZui.com and the KidZui browser, and not for any other purpose. We may, however, share information about our users in the aggregate, as necessary, with third party service providers that help us run the site or perform certain functions on our behalf. These providers are prohibited from using any information we share with them for their own benefit.

We may also share non-personal information about our users with third parties for advertising purposes. Such data is also only shared in the aggregate to provide advertisers with basic information related to our total user base in the aggregate.

Finally, the Website may disclose user information, including Personal Information, if any, that we may have collected, in order to respond to a subpoena, court order, law enforcement request, user safety issue, or as otherwise required by law. Your information may also be transferred to a third party in the event that we file for bankruptcy or are involved in an acquisition, merger, sale, corporate reorganization or other similar event.

## IV. SECURITY

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures in an effort to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to information supplied by or obtained from visitors to our Website. For example, we limit the number of people who have physical access to our database servers and use electronic security systems and password protections to guard against unauthorized access. We also take reasonable steps to help make sure that third-parties having access to information collected on our Website keep such information confidential and use it solely in compliance with this Policy. Information collected at the Websites will not be stored for longer than is necessary for the purposes described in this Policy, or to otherwise meet legal requirements.

Despite these measures, no method of security is 100 percent secure and, therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your data.

V. PARENTAL REVIEW OF INFORMATION

Parents always have the option to review their child’s Website account ("Account"), disable or cancel the Account , correct factual errors in any information contained in the Account or request the deletion of any information contained in the Account. Parents may also request that we discontinue further collection or use of your child’s Personal Information (if we have any on file).

Parents interested in accessing the Account for the purposes outlined above should use the contact information in the Section VII below. Parents can review information that has been collected about children who are 12 or under using either of the following 2 methods:

Parents can review their child’s information by logging into the parental account that is created once the registration is approved by going to http://www.KidZui.com. You will need to have your e-mail address that you used to sign-up and the password you selected at sign-up.

You can also contact KidZui Customer Support to view the information that has been collected from or about your child by sending an email to support@kidzui.com. You will need to have your parent login information (e-mail address) as well as your child’s user name and password to enable us to answer your questions.

When we receive your cancellation request, we will permanently delete all information associated with the Account from our database. Please note that if you deactivate the Account, this action may result in the permanent termination of the Account, as well as any points or achievements earned under that Account.

We also offer a version of the Kidzui browser which enables the parent or guardian to act as an "administrator" and monitor and review information regarding the child’s Internet activity (e.g., what web pages they have visited, what pictures and videos they have viewed, and how much time the child has spent online).

## VI.  YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to or write us at the address set forth in Section VII below.

## VII. CONTACT US

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our Policy and/or practices, please contact us at the following e-mail and mailing addresses:

Email: support@kidzui.com

Mailing Address:

Privacy Manager

KidZui, Inc.,

4350 Executive Drive, Suite 300,

San Diego CA 92121.

VIII. UPDATES & EFFECTIVE DATE

From time to time, we may update this Policy. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Except as otherwise provided, such modifications will become effective on the day they are posted.

IX. GOVERNING LAW

Our Website is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the U.S. We make no representation that the Website is operated in accordance with the laws of any other jurisdiction. Your continued use of the Website indicates that you are agreeing to the collection, use, disclosure, management and storage of your Personal Information will as described in this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of the Policy, you should promptly discontinue using the Website. You should also contact us to advise how you would like us to handle any Personal Information that we may have previously collected from you. 

(1) Personal information as defined by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") means individually identifiable information about an individual collected online, including: (i) a first and last name; (ii) a home or other physical address including street name and name of a city or town; (iii) online contact information; (iv) a screen or user name where it functions in the same manner as online contact information; (v) a telephone number; (vi) a Social Security number; (vii) a persistent identifier that can be used to recognize a user over time and across different websites or online services. Such persistent identifier includes, but is not limited to, a customer number held in a cookie, an Internet Protocol (IP) address, a processor or device serial number, or unique device identifier; (viii) a photograph, video, or audio file where such file contains a child’s image or voice; (ix) geo-location information sufficient to identify street name and name of a city or town; or (x) information concerning the child or the parents of that child that the operator collects online from the child and combines with an identifier described in this definition.

(2) Behavioral advertising is advertising that is specifically targeted to an individual based upon the individual's browsing activities on the website or on the web in general.
